# YOUN SOO LIM

(604) 364-8470 yslim.bcit@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/younsoo-lim younsoolim.com



# Creative and Skillful Web Development Student at BCIT

Passionate about front-end development. I am excited to bring my creativity and marketing expertise to digital design and development through my previous professional experience in design and manufacturing.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Front-End Developer, UX/UI Designer — MyLandlord | Next.js, React, React UI

Vancouver, Canada

SEPTEMBER 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

- Created prototypes, managed brand quality consistency and designed high-quality graphic images.
- Collaborated with back-end developers, full-stack students, on improving usability.
- Created user-friendly web pages by using markup languages, such as React, Next.js.

# Front-End Developer, UX/UI Designer — reVamp | Next.js, React

Vancouver, Canada

JANUARY 2021 - MAY 2021

- Contributed to all stages of development, including planning, testing, and coding.
- Constructed a user-interactive site architecture.
- Built reusable and scalable code and components.

# **Web Developer, UX/UI Designer** — irl\_Dater | Figma, HTML, CSS, jQuery

Vancouver, Canada

MARCH 2021 - MAY 2021

- Collected, researched, investigated and evaluated user requirements.
- Provided an exceptional user experience through intuitive application design.
- Designed and developed a marketing website for the application.

## • R&D Senior Team Manager — Hansae Fashion Worldwide,

Seoul, Korea

MAY 2018 — OCTOBER 2019

- Led a Design Team of nine members. Trained members, provided design direction, and solved problems.
- Assisted team members in developing their skills and growing in their roles.

# R&D Senior Team Manager — Pan Pacific,

Seoul, Korea

OCTOBER 2014 - MAY 2018

- Planned, created, and presented knit performance and women's wear for American and European buyers.
- Designed clothes with solid brand identities based on understanding customers' needs and marketing objectives.

### Merchandiser — 2 and 1, MU Sports,

Tokyo, Japan

MAY 2014 — OCTOBER 2014

- Planned and coordinated the international shipment of goods.
- Communicated and negotiated with shippers, agents, buyers, and vendors.

# R&D Senior Designer / Assistant Manager — Hansae Fashion Worldwide,

Seoul, Korea

APRIL 2006 - JULY 2011

- Analyzed, designed, and delivered ladies' wear, active, intimate, loungewear, and junior wear for American buyers.
- Worked independently with minimal supervision.

# **Technical Designer** − Marc Ecko Enterprises,

New York, USA

SEPTEMBER 2003 — SEPTEMBER 2005

- Created urban-style men's and women's wear tech packs in a start-up brand.
- Collaborated with designers, providing technical adjustments and supporting the design process.

## Assistant Visual Merchandiser — Bloomingdale's,

New York, USA

AUGUST 2002 — APRIL 2003

- Supported stock sell-through by creating a visual appeal for customers in the store.
- Proactively managed workloads and deadlines and communicated trade-offs.

### **PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES**

### Front-end Development

HTML, CSS JavaScript, jQuery React, Next.js, WordPress MySQL, MongoDB

### **UI/UX** Design

Figma

### Graphic Design

Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign

#### SKILLS

Strong analysis, problem-solving, troubleshooting

Solid contribution to a team

Self-learning

Adaptability

Leadership and team management

Time management and prioritization

Collaboration

Communication and presentation

Visual design and product design

Prototyping, wireframing, user flows

### **LANGUAGES**

English Full professional proficiency

Korean Native proficiency

Japanese Limited working proficiency

# YOUN SOO LIM

(604) 364-8470 yslim.bcit@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/younsoo-lim younsoolim.com



# Creative and Skillful Web Development Student at BCIT

Passionate about front-end development. I am excited to bring my creativity and marketing expertise to digital design and development through my previous professional experience in design and manufacturing.

### **EDUCATION**

# Digital Design and Development | Diploma —

British Columbia Institute of Technology, Vancouver, BC SEPTEMBER 2020 – MAY 2022

• Developed a solid foundation in designing, developing, and creating interactive, dynamic, immersive social and online applications across a multi-platforms.

# Global Fashion Management | Master of Professional Studies —

Fashion Institute of Technology, New York, USA

AUGUST 2011 - DECEMBER 2012

• Be prepared for top management and leadership positions in the international fashion industry as an emerging executive.

# **Visual Presentation and Exhibit Design** | Associate in Applied Science –

Fashion Institute of Technology, New York, USA

AUGUST 2000 - MAY 2002

Developed skill sets to work in exhibition design, retail design, product displays, special
events, screen and stage design, and brand environments.

# Fashion Design | Bachelor's Degree of Fine Art —

Ewha Womans University, Seoul, Korea

MARCH 1995 - FEBRUARY 1999

• Educated in fashion and related businesses as a highly creative and professional individual with expert knowledge.

# PROJECTS

natiive | HTML, CSS, jQuery

SEPTEMBER 2021 - OCTOBER 2021

### Website that educates information about indigenous people in British Columbia

- Gathered and refined specifications and requirements based on technical requirements.
- Developed website layouts and user interfaces using HTML, CSS, and jQuery.
- Ensured workload balance by maintaining workflows with team members.

## **About\_Kingdom** | WordPress

JANUARY 2021 - MARCH 2021

### Blog site that provides information about the Korean drama series, The Kingdom

- Designed, implemented, and managed websites using WordPress.
- Utilized and customized WordPress plug-ins and themes.
- Formulated an effective and responsive design.

#### **AWARDS**

### Summa Cum Laude (Dean's List)

Awarded by Fashion Institute of Technology in 2002.

### Honourable Mention

Awarded an Honorable Mention for the design of a centerpiece for the UN Plaza Ballroom's "Salute to the Stars" event in 2002.

# Magna Cum Laude (Dean's list)

Awarded by Ewha Womans University in 1999.